[
	{
		"question": "What do you call a Mexican jedi?",
		"answer": "Obi-Juan Kenobi"
	},
	{
		"question": "What do Gungans put things in?",
		"answer": "Jar Jars"
		},
	{
		"question": "What do you call a Sith who won't fight?",
		"answer": "A Sithy"
		},
	{
		"question": "Where does Princess Liea go shopping for clothes?",
		"answer": "The Darth Maul"
		},
	{
		"question": "How do Ewoks communicate over long distances?",
		"answer": "Ewokie Talkies"
		},
	{
		"question": "What do Jedi use to open PDF files?",
		"answer": "Adobe Wan Kenobi"
		},
	{
		"question": "What website shares secrets of the Sith Empire?",
		"answer": "Wookieleaks"
		},
	{
		"question": "What do you call a pirate droid?",
		"answer": "Argh2-D2"
		},
	{
		"question": "Where does Jabba the Hutt eat?",
		"answer": "Pizza Hutt"
		},
	{
		"question": "What do you call a Jedi who loves tacos?",
		"answer": "Obi-Juan Kenobi"
		},
	{
		"question": "Why should you never tell jokes on the Falcon?",
		"answer": "The ship might crack up."
		},
	{
		"question": "What do you call a potato that has turned to the Dark side?",
		"answer": "Vader Tots"
		},
	{
		"question": "How many Sith does it take to screw in a hyperdrive?",
		"answer": "Two, but I donâ€™t know how they got in it."
	}
]
